A Guide to the University of Virginia Dean of the Curry School of Education Office Administrative Files, 1970-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Dean of the Curry School of Education Office Administrative Files 1970-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-10/1/1.861
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from Richard M. Brandt, Curry School of Education, University of Virginia on November 1, 1986.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of general records of the Office of the Dean of the Curry School of Education during the tenure of Richard M. Brandt.
Topics include AACTE (American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education), Association of Colleges and Schools of Education in State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (ACSESULGC), administrative committees, American Educational Research Association, alumni, annual reports, budget, Bureau of Education Researchs, continuing education, Education Day, fifth year program, minority affairs, reorganization, retreats, special education, State Council of Higher Education in Virginia, summer session, Virginia Association of College for Teacher Education (VACTE), faculty and personnel, off-ground programs, and general correspondence.
Contents List
- Office Administrative Files
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education (AACTE), 1979-1980 (Folder 1)
  - AACTE Directory, 1980 (Folder 1)
  - AACTE Minutes and Printed Material, 1979-1980 (Folder 1)
  - AACTE Human Services Task Force, 1980 (Folder 1)
  - AACTE Survey, 1981 (Folder 1)
  - Association of Colleges and Schools of Education in State Universities and Land Grant Colleges [ACSESULGC]- Winter, 1977-1978 (Folder 1)
  - ACSESULGC- Arizona, 1979 (Folder 1)
  - ACSESULGC- Boston, 1978 (Folder 1)
  - ACSESULGC- Chicago, 1978 (Folder 1)
  - ACSESULGC- Dallas, 1979 (Folder 1)
  - ACSESULGC-Dallas, 1978-1979 (Folder 1)
  - Advisory Council of State Representatives, 1978 (Folder 1)
  - Administrative Committee, 1977 (Folder 2)
  - Administrative Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 2)
  - Administrative Committee, 1979-1980 (Folder 2)
  - Administrative Committee, 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council Retreat, 1975 (Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council Retreat, 1976-1977 (Folder 2)
  - Admissions Report, 1974-1975 (Folder 2)
  - Admissions Report, 1975-1976 (Folder 2)
  - Admissions and Student Offices Matters, 1978-1980 (Folder 2)
  - Advisory Council of State Representatives- St. Louis, 1979 (Folder 2)
  - American Educational Research Association [AERA], 1980, 2 folders. (Folder 2)
  - AERA- Washington D.C., 1980 (Folder 3)
  - Agreements, 1975-1976 (Folder 3)
  - Alumni, 1980-1981 (Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Application for Grants Under Teachers Corps, 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Approved Program Review, 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Association of Education Students, 1974-1976 (Folder 3)
  - Association of Education Students, 1976-1978 (Folder 3)
  - BEH Project, 1975 (Folder 3)
  - Berea College Conference, 1980 (Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1982-1983 (Folder 3)
  - Bureau of Teaching Materials, 1980 (Folder 3)
  - Bureau of Education Research, Prior to 1975 (Folder 3)
  - Bureau of Education Research, 1978-1980 (Folder 3)
  - Business Industry Education Roles, 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Capital Campaign, 1980-1981 (Folder 3)
  - Career Education, 1977 (Folder 3)
  - Catlin/Trent, 1974 (Folder 4)
  - Center for Teaching Effectiveness, 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Chicago Meeting, 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Chicago Resource Seminar, 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Child Development Center, 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Community Education, 1980, 2 folders. (Folder 4)
  - Consortia, 1981-1982 (Folder 4)
  - Consulting Policy, 1979 (Folder 4)
  - Consultative Research Center, Prior to 1977 (Folder 4)
  - Consultative Research Center, 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education Colloquium, 1981 (Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1977 January-February (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1977 March (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1977 June (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1977 July (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1977 August (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1977 September-October (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1977 November- December (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1978 January- March (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1978 April-June (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1978 Fall (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Correspondence, 1978-1979 Winter (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Course Plans, 1979 (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education Meeting, 1978 November (Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education General Affairs, 1981-1982 (Folder 5)
  - Contributors, 1975-1978 (Folder 5)
  - Core Requirements, 1975-1976 (Folder 5)
  - Council on Postsecondary Accreditation, 1978 (Folder 5)
  - Counseling Psychology, 1977 (Folder 5)
  - Cox, Charlie, 1980-1981 (Folder 5)
  - DC Schools Teacher Center, 1974-1975 (Folder 5)
  - Davies, Gordon, 1979-1982 (Folder 5)
  - Dean Brandt, 1979 (Folder 5)
  - Dean Brandt, 1980 (Folder 5)
  - Deans' Meetings with Shannon, 1975-1976 (Folder 5)
  - Deans' Meetings with Shannon, 1977-1978 (Folder 5)
  - Deans' Meetings with Shannon, 1978-1979 (Folder 6)
  - Distinguished Alumnus Award, 1975 (Folder 6)
  - Drug Abuse- Complaint Stage, 1975 (Folder 5)
  - Drug Abuse Program- Report on Audit, 1977 (Folder 6)
  - EdD/PhD Distinction, 1976-1977 (Folder 6)
  - Education Bills, 1981 (Folder 6)
  - Education Clinics Advisory Committee, 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Educational Motion Pictures, 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Education Day, 1976 (Folder 6)
  - Education Day, 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Education Day, 1979 (Folder 6)
  - Education Day, 1980 (Folder 6)
  - Education Day Follow-Up Business, 1980 (Folder 6)
  - Education Day Photos, 1975 (Folder 6)
  - Education Day Speech, 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Education Foundation, 1977-1978 (Folder 6)
  - Education Improvement Research, 1978 (Folder 7)
  - Education Research Capacity Report, 1981 (Folder 7)
  - Endowed Research Center Plans, 1982 (Folder 7)
  - Enrollment Information, 1974-1975 (Folder 7)
  - Environmental Education, 1980 (Folder 7)
  - Evaluation Research Center, 1975, 2 folders. (Folder 7)
  - Evaluation Training Consortium Project, 1975, 2 folders. (Folder 7)
  - Evaluation Training Consortium Workshop, 1974-1975 (Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1978 (Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1979 (Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1980 (Folder 7)
  - FBI Program (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Folder 7)
  - FBI Program (2 of 2), 1977 (Folder 8)
  - FBI Summer (2 folders), 1977 (Folder 8)
  - Fifth Year Internship History, 1978 (Folder 1978)
  - Fifth Year Program- Other Colleges, 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Fifth Year Program- Position and Documentation, 1977 (Folder 8)
  - Fifth Year Program- Questionnaire, 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Fifth Year Program- Reactions and Plans, 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Fifth Year Position on Requirements, 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Fifth Year Program- State Department Action, 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Foundation Board Meeting, 1977 (Folder 8)
  - Foundation Board Meeting, 1979 (Folder 8)
  - Foundation Board Meeting, 1980 (Folder 8)
  - Fraternities- AES, PDK, KDP, 1977-1980 (Folder 8)
  - Gifts, 1976,1980 (Folder 9)
  - Gilley, Wade, n.d. (Folder 9)
  - Graduation, 1978-1980 (Folder 9)
  - Graduate Instructors, 1977 (Folder 9)
  - House Education Sub-Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 9)
  - House Joint Resolution 100, 1980 (Folder 9)
  - Human Resource Specialist Committee, 1980 (Folder 9)
  - HVR 165 Committee, 1978 (Folder 9)
  - In-Service Training, 1978 (Folder 9)
  - Institute for Study of Social and Legal Change [ISSLC], 1980-1981 (Folder 9)
  - ISSLC- Conflicting Regulations, 1982 (Folder 9)
  - Land Grant Deans Association- General, 1979 (Folder 9)
  - Leadership Development Meeting, 1980 (Folder 10)
  - Legislation Affecting Programs, 1977-1978 (Folder 10)
  - Legislation- VACTE, 1978 (Folder 10)
  - Legislative Bills, 1980-1981 (Folder 10)
  - Legislature, 1981 (Folder 10)
  - Lewin and Associates, 1974-1976 (Folder 10)
  - Medical School Memoranda, 1979-1980 (Folder 10)
  - Middle School Survey, 1975 (Folder 10)
  - Minnesota Mission, 1979 (Folder 10)
  - Minority Affairs (1-3 of 5), 1972-1980 (Folder 10)
  - Minority Affairs (4-5 of 5), 1972-1980 (Folder 11)
  - Minority Study in Teacher Education, 1975-1976, 2 folders. (Folder 11)
  - Measurement and Evaluation Plans, 1978 (Folder 11)
  - Membership Meeting, 1978 (Folder 11)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1980 (Folder 11)
  - National Teachers Exam, 1976-1978 (Folder 11)
  - National Teachers Exam Adoption, 1981 (Folder 11)
  - National Teachers Exam Background Materials, 1970-1979 (Folder 11)
  - National Teachers Exam Court Cases- Florida and South Carolina, 1977, 2 folders. (Folder 12)
  - National Teachers Exam Sub-Committee, 1979 (Folder 12)
  - Needs Assessment, 1975 (Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1978-1979 (Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1979-1980 (Folder 12)
  - NIE 1975 (Folder 12)
  - Northern Virginia Consortium Crisis, 1981 (Folder 12)
  - Northern Virginia Programs, 1981-1982 (Folder 12)
  - Outstanding Professor Award, 1980 (Folder 12)
  - Outstanding Student Award, 1979 (Folder 12)
  - Printed Material, 1980 (Folder 12)
  - Printed Material, 1980 (Folder 12)
  - Problems- Budget and Local, 1975-1977 (Folder 12)
  - Professional Standards Committee, 1978, 2 folders. (Folder 12)
  - Redraft Considerations and General Notes, 1975, 2 folders. (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization Plans, 1969-1977, 2 folders. (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization Plans, 1969-1977, 3 folders. (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization-Evaluation of Governing System, 1978 (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization- Final Documents, 1980 (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization- Faculty Commission, 1980 (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization- Faculty Meeting (audio tape), 1980 (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization- Letters, 1980 (Folder 13)
  - Reorganization- Miscellaneous, 1979-1980
  - Reorganization- Research Plans, 1980 (Folder 14)
  - Reorganization-Strategies, 1980 (Folder 14)
  - Research Committee for PhD, 1975-1978 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat #1, 1978 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat #2, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat #1 and #2 Follow-Up, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat Feedback, 1979-1980 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat Synthesis, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat, 1981 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Administrative, 1978 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Adult Education, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Afton, 1980 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Field Activities, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Graves, 1975 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Policies Study, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Rehabilitation, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat- Teachers Education, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Retreat-(folder 1 of 2), 1979, Audio tapes/7 inch. (Folder 14)
  - Retreat (folder 2 of 2), 1979, Audio Tapes/7 inch. (Folder 15)
  - Rhode Island Teacher Centers, 1974-1975 (Folder 15)
  - Richmond Meeting (2 folders), 1976 (Folder 15)
  - Robinson, Adelle, 1977-1979 (Folder 15)
  - School of Education Documents, 1975 (Folder 15)
  - SCE- Early Meetings, 1976 (Folder 15)
  - SCE- Trends, 1977 (Folder 15)
  - School Council (3 folders), 1979-1981 (Folder 16)
  - School of Education Analysis, 1975 (Folder 16)
  - Secondary Health Education, 1976 (Folder 16)
  - Special Education Department, 1982-1983 (Folder 16)
  - Special Education Department, 1982-1983 (Folder 16)
  - Special Education Documents, 1979-1980 (Folder 16)
  - Special Education Plans, 1979 (Folder 16)
  - Special Education Proposal, 1981 (Folder 16)
  - Special Education Task Force (2 folders), 1980 (Folder 16)
  - Staff Studies- HVR 165, 1978 (Folder 16)
  - Stahl/Nelson Visit, 1976 (Folder 16)
  - Standards for State Approval of Teacher Education, 1976 (Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV), 1970-1976 (Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1977-1978 (Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1980 (Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1981 (Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education- Cancelled Programs, 1981 (Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education-Draft of Teacher Education Paper, 1981 October (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1977 March (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1977 May (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1977 August (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1978 May (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1978 December (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1979 May (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1980 February (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee Meeting, 1980 May (Folder 17)
  - State Advisory Committee on Teacher Competency Exams, 1978 (Folder 18)
  - State Advisory Sub-Committee on Teacher Education, 1978 (Folder 18)
  - State Advisory Committee- Sub-Committee on Teacher Testing, 1978-1979 (Folder 18)
  - State Presidents Meeting- St. Louis, 1979 (Folder 18)
  - Statewide Higher Education, 1979 (Folder 18)
  - Statistical Information, 1977-1979 (Folder 18)
  - Strap Project Reports (2 folders), 1974 (Folder 18)
  - Summer Conference- Radford, 1975 (Folder 18)
  - Summer Conference, 1977 (Folder 18)
  - Summer Session, 1974 (Folder 18)
  - Summer Session, 1976 (Folder 18)
  - Summer Session, 1978 (Folder 18)
  - Summer- VACTE, 1980 (Folder 18)
  - Summer Workshop- GMU, 1979 (Folder 18)
  - Summer Workshop Conference, 1980 (Folder 18)
  - Superintendent of Public Instruction- S. John Davis, 1979 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Activities, 1978-1979 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Conference- Capon Springs, 1977-1978 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Meeting, 1977 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents- Memos, 1977-1978 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Seminar, 1978 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Study Group Materials, 1976-1977 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Study Group Materials, 1977-1978 (Folder 19)
  - Superintendents Study Group Materials, 1978-1979 (Folder 19)
  - Task Force, 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Teacher Competency Exam [see also "State Advisory Committee"], 1978 (Folder 19)
  - Teacher Competency Test, 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Teacher Education, 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Teacher Education Advisory Committee, 1979 (Folder 19)
  - Teacher Education Advisory Committee- Recertification, 1977-1978 (Folder 19)
  - Teacher Preparation Programs, 1979 (Folder 19)
  - Teacher Training Report, 1981 (Folder 19)
  - Trainers of Teacher Trainers Program, 1981 (Folder 19)
  - UCEA Austin (Texas), 1982 (Folder 19)
  - Virginia Association of Children with Learning Disabilities, 1976-1979 (Folder 19)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education [VACTE], 1975-1976 (Folder 19)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education- General, 1976-1977 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education-General (Cassette Tapes), 1977 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education-General (Including constitution), 1977-1978 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education-General, 1978 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education- ODU Conference, 1976 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education-Lynchburg College, 1978 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education Meeting, 1978 September (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education Meeting, 1978 November (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education Meeting, 1979 January (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1979 April (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1979 June (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Business, 1979 July/October (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1979 October (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1979 December (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1980 January (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Business, 1980 February/March (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Business, 1980 April/July (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1980 April (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1980 October (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teachers Education Meeting, 1980 December (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education- Preparation of Teachers, 1975 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education Review Committee, 1981 (Folder 20)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education- Revisions to Constitution, 1976-1977 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education Nominating Committee, 1980 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Association of Colleges for Teacher Education Out-of-State Institutions, 1977 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Association of School Administrators, 1978-1979 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Association of School Administrators Newsletters, 1976-1981 (Folder 21)
  - VASSP, 1981 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Code Commission Report, 1980 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1976-1977 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Council on Economic Education, 1981 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Council on Economic Education, 1981 (Folder 21)
  - Virginia Plan for Higher Education, 1979 (Folder 21)
  - Wisconsin Mission, 1980 (Folder 21)
  - Youth and Family Studies, 1974-1978 (Folder 21)
- Faculty and Personnel
  - Department of Administration and Supervision Position, 1978 (Folder 22)
  - Aderson, Bill: Clinical Child Psychology, 1981 (Folder 22)
  - Associated Dean Position, 1976 (Folder 22)
  - Associated Dean for Research, 1980-1981 (Folder 22)
  - Banks, James, 1978 (Folder 22)
  - Black Faculty Proposals, 1980-1981 (Folder 22)
  - Brown, Bob, 1981 (Folder 22)
  - Child Psychology Position, 1975 (Folder 22)
  - Coordinator for Student Affairs Search, 1979 (Folder 22)
  - Counselor of Education Position, 1977 (Folder 22)
  - Counselor of Education Position, 1981 (Folder 22)
  - Curriculum and Instruction Position, 1977 (Folder 22)
  - Early Childhood Position, 1980 (Folder 22)
  - Early Childhood Position, 1981 (Folder 22)
  - Educational Research Program Evaluation, 1980-1981 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty, 1975 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Activity Plan, 1981 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1978-1980 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1980-1981 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Affairs Committee, 1981-1982 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Assignments, 1980 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Bulletins, 1979 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Development Retreat, 1978 (Folder 22)
  - Faculty Development, 1980-1982 (Folder 23)
  - Faculty Development Newsletter, 1978 (Folder 23)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1975 (Folder 23)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1978 (Folder 23)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1979-1980 (Folder 23)
  - Faculty Recruiting, 1980-1981 (Folder 23)
  - Faculty Vacancies, 1975-1977 (Folder 23)
  - Head Teacher Position, 1980 (Folder 23)
  - Health and Physical Education Search Committee for New Chairman (2 folders), 1976-1977 (Folder 23)
  - Health Education Position, 1981 (Folder 23)
  - Higher Education Position, 1976, 1980 (Folder 23)
  - Instructional Media Position, 1975-1976 (Folder 23)
  - Job Applicants of Special Interest, 1978 (Folder 23)
  - Philosophy/Social Foundations Position, 1977 (Folder 23)
  - Powell Position, 1977 (Folder 23)
  - Reading Position, 1976 (Folder 23)
  - Recruiting Activity for Fall, 1977-1978 (Folder 23)
  - Rehabillitation Counselor Position, 1977 (Folder 23)
  - Research Faculty- Wes McDonald, 1980 (Folder 23)
  - Research Methodology- Donald M. Medley, 1972-1974 (Folder 23)
  - Richards, Colin, 1980 (Folder 24)
  - Special Education Position, 1977 (Folder 24)
  - Speech Pathology Position, 1975 (Folder 24)
  - Social Foundations Position, 1980 (Folder 24)
  - Social Studies Education Position, 1976 (Folder 24)
  - Teacher Centers, 1978 (Folder 24)
  - Teachers Corps, 1978 (Folder 24)
  - Teachers Corps Proposal, 1978 (Folder 24)
  - Teachers Corps Proposal Committee, 1979 (Folder 24)
  - Teachers Corps- Fluvanna, 1977-1978 (Folder 24)
  - Teachers Corps- National Conference Report, 1977 (Folder 24)
  - Teachers Corps- Wise County, 1976-1977 (Folder 24)
  - Teacher Education Position, 1979-1980 (Folder 24)
  - Vacancies, 1977-1978 (Folder 24)
  - Visually Impaired Program Position, 1976 (Folder 24)
- Off-Grounds Programs
  - Abingdon- Elementary Education, 1973-1975 (Folder 25)
  - Averett College Case, 1979-1982 (Folder 25)
  - Berry, W. C.- Field Instruction and Research, 1975 (Folder 25)
  - Birdwood Residential College, 1978-1979 (Folder 25)
  - Bridgewater College, 1978 (Folder 25)
  - Central Virginia Consortium, 1978 (Folder 25)
  - Chesapeake Meeting, 1976 (Folder 25)
  - Claypool Hill- Elementary Education, n.d. (Folder 25)
  - Community College Meeting, 1980 (Folder 25)
  - Community College System, 1976-1979 (Folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Plan- Capitol Consortium, 1976 (Folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Plan- Central Virginia Consortium, 1976 (Folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Plan- Valley of Virginia Consortium, 1976 (Folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Plan- Virginia Tidewater Consortium, 1976 (Box-folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Plan- Western Region Consortium, 1976 (Folder 25)
  - Consortia Documents- State Council, 1974-1979 (Folder 25)
  - Cooperative Plans- In-State Universities, 1975-1980 (Folder 26)
  - Danville- Elementary Education, n.d. (Folder 26)
  - Danville Pittsylvania Laboratory School, 1976 (Folder 26)
  - Fall Semester- Off-Grounds, 1979 (Folder 26)
  - Fairfax County, 1975 (Folder 26)
  - Field Programs Conference, 1979 (Folder 26)
  - GWU External Teacher Center Project, 1975 (Folder 26)
  - Henry County- Elementary Education, n.d. (Folder 26)
  - London Program- Summer, 1982 (Folder 26)
  - Longwood College, 1982 (Folder 26)
  - Margaret Cushen- British Education, 1975 (Folder 26)
  - Mary Washington, 1977-1979 (Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Off-Grounds, 1981-1983 (Folder 26)
  - Nelson County, 1978 (Folder 26)
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) Consortium Meetings, 1975-1977 (Folder 26)
  - Northern Virginia Continuing Education, 1978 (Folder 26)
  - Northern Virginia Realigning Report, 1976 (Folder 26)
  - Off- Campus Activities Survey, 1980 (Folder 26)
  - Off-Campus Study, 1982 (Folder 27)
  - Off-Grounds Program- General (2 folders), 1977 (Folder 27)
  - Off-Grounds Program- General, 1978 (Folder 27)
  - Off-Grounds Program- General, 1980 (Folder 27)
  - Off-Grounds Masters Degree Program, 1975 (Folder 27)
  - Off-Grounds Planning, 1976-1977 (Folder 27)
  - Off-Grounds Search Committee, 1981 (Folder 27)
  - Printed Material, 1976, 1980 (Folder 27)
  - Problems- Other Locations, 1975-1976 (Folder 27)
  - Roanoke- Administration and Supervision, n.d. (Folder 27)
  - Roanoke- Continuing Education, 1974 (Folder 27)
  - School of Continuing Education- George Mason, 1974-1975 (Folder 27)
  - Southwest Virginia Masters Degree Program, 1973 (Folder 27)
  - Senate Review of Off-Grounds Program, 1976-1977 (Folder 28)
  - Summer Laboratory School, 1976 (Folder 28)
  - Summer Semester, 1979 (Folder 28)